

# Ahsan Razzaq Graphic Designer

**3** 0092-3006981869

② House # 129, St # 2, Amin Park, Lahore

Flexworld.pk@gmail.com

#### About Me

Highly Creative and multi-talented Graphic Designer with innovative experience in multimedia, marketing and print design. I have collaborated with creative team to design and produce computer generated artwork for marketing and promotional materials. Participated in production of print and promotional items for key clients under direction of Marketing Department.

## Education

MBA(Finance)

University of South Asia, Lahore

2009 - 2011

**B.Com** 

Islamia University, Bahawalpur

2008

## Experience

**Graphic Designer** 

Print World

Faislabad, Pakistan 2012 - 2016

**Graphic Designer** 

Flex World

Chistian, Pakistan 2016 - Present

#### **Skills**

Dhatashan	
Photoshop	
•	

CorelDraw

Illustrator

MS Office

## Reference

Flex World (Printing Press)

Manager

0092-3366986666

**Print World (Printing Press)** 

Manager

0092-3336336483

## **Hobbies**







Lifestyle



Reading Football



Swimming



Painting